-[Kinger]: [snoring]
-[Caine]: [over speakers]
Rise and shine, sleepy head!
-[Kinger]: What?
Who's there?
-[Caine]: [sing-song]
I've got another pop-up for you!
-[Kinger]: Yeah, that's gonna be
a big no from me.
-[Caine]: No, no, Kinger-boy.
I'm not being ignored by you any more.
-[Kinger]: WHAT?
[coughs]
-[Caine]: If you don't love me,
maybe I'll find someone else who will.
-[Queenie]: Help me!!
-[Kinger]: W-WIFE?!
-[Queenie]: Kinger!
-[Kinger]: Wife!
-[Queenie]: How did you
even get here?
-[Kinger]: No time!
We gotta go before --
-[Caine]: [babbles]
[screams]
-[Kinger]: OH!
Where am I?!
-[Pomni]: Whoa there, Kinger.
Just relax, okay?
You really knocked your head hard.
-[Ragatha]: Oh, it's good
to see you up again, Kinger.
We were worried about you.
-[Kinger]: Oh, it was just terrible!
I had this --
-[Narrator]: [monotone] Wonderful dream
about the all-new Caine puppet
and Queenie plush,
along with the release
of new Animatez figurines.
-[Ragatha]:
Wait, they tried to sell you --
-[Narrator]:
The incredible Kinger pendant
and sideshow Animiniz,
both with their own
super rare figures to collect.
-[Ragatha]: Wow.
That's, uh --
-[Narrator]: 20% off Digital Circus items
for a limited time only.
-[Pomni]: Well, we're just happy
to have you back.
-[Kinger]: Yep.
There's no place like --
-[Narrator]: digitalcircus.store
[terrifying antiquated audio blares]